Kettle and Idol
Now, please introduce your announcement from Ms. Murahoshi. Go ahead!
Yes, I have an announcement. Ukka's one-man live show this year has been scheduled.
Crescendo at BEATS Shibuya on Saturday, September 30
and "Deja Vu" at Tokyo Kinema Club on Saturday, October 14.
This is the first time for me to do two one-man shows.
It's my first time. They are coming soon.
Are the two different titles going to have different contents?
Yes, they are. I think the way the songs in the set will be arranged will be different,
Both one-man shows will be different, so please come and enjoy them. Please come and enjoy them.
And one more thing. Here it is!
On Sunday, October 29th, at Yokohama Arena, Stapla Idol Festival Autumn New Song Harvest Festival will be held, and all the groups will perform for the first time.
This time, all the groups will be performing one of their new songs, which will be performed for the first time,
I don't think they have decided what they will perform yet,
I don't think they have decided what they are going to play yet, but I guess everyone should look forward to it.
Yes, I think so. Yes, that's right. All the groups will perform their new songs for the first time,
I am looking forward to seeing what kind of new songs they will play.
Please come and enjoy the show. Please do.
I've been asking you a question every time, Yaasan-kun,
I'm always asking you questions, Yaasan-kun, about the Star Pride Festival and the many idols from STAPLA,
Do you want to take a picture with someone?
Do you want to take a picture with someone or make friends with this girl? This time.
Every year, or rather, at the live shows where all the STAPLA idols gather, or at the live shows at the STAPLA Festivals,
I would like to take a picture with Kanako Momota of Momoiro Clover Z.
There was another Staplafest this year,
I was not able to take a picture of her because of various reasons,
October this year,
I think it means that she went back with a heart of light from October,
But I saw the moment.
I could see it. But you were originally from Shizuoka?
When I was in the fourth grade, I lived in Hamamatsu City, Shizuoka Prefecture, for one year,
I went to the elementary school that Kanako went to.
Kanako came to give a class at my old school when I was in March,
I was able to meet her there for the first time.
Because of this connection, I hope that you will do your best to take pictures with Kanako.
Finally, Yakan-kun will give you a cup of tea to cheer you up!
Thank you very much.
This time
It is a blend of herbal teas to soothe your throat!
Please enjoy!
Bon appétit!
Wow.
A teacup, a teacup, a teacup. Thank you very much.
It's delicious, the herb tea is fragrant and aromatic. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I hope you will do your best with the help of the chest feathers.
Yes, sir.
Now then, please give us a cute closing remark.
Yes, everyone.
Thank you very much for watching this interview with Yakan and his idol, Yakan-kun.
If you are interested in this interview, please come and see us at our one-man live concert,
I hope you will come to Ucka's one-man live concert.
That's all for now, this is Director Murahoshi of Ukka. Thank you very much.
This program is,
Mr. Naoki Star
Mr. Pom Pom Hide
Mr. Ine Ine
Mr. Shinkai
This program was provided by Mr. Sosuke Suminoe. Thank you all very much for your contributions!
Let's work hard together tomorrow!
끝!